Guide to the Merrill G. Burlingame Papers 1880-1990
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Photographs, 11
  - Bozeman #113-126 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Gallatin Valley Female Seminary, circa 1930s (Box 71, Folder 9, Photographic-print 115-126)
    - Bozeman and Gallatin County (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 127-136)
    - Mary M. Timmons, Bozeman's First Born (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 127)
    - Commercial National Bank (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 128)
    - Presbyterian church (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 129)
    - BPOE building (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 130)
    - Main Street, 1908 (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 131)
    - Big Horn Gun, courthouse (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 132)
    - Interior, Eric Alson home (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 133-134)
    - Bozeman Business and Professional Women, circa 1930s (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 135)
    - Bozeman Rotary Club, circa 1920s (Box 71, Folder 10, Photographic-print 136)
  - Emigrant Gulch and the Yellowstone Gold Mining Co. #137-145 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Emigrant Gulch and the Yellowstone Gold Mining Co. (Box 71, Folder 11, Photographic-print 137-145)
  - Monuments and tombstones #146-165 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Missouri headwaters (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 146)
    - W.J. Sayre (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 147)
    - Henry T. Comstock (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 148)
    - Jim Winters (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 149)
    - Lemhi County monument (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 150)
    - Lemhi County monument (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 151)
    - Old Iron Foundry, Utah (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 152)
    - Wibaux grave markers (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 153-155)
    - Hershman gravesite, Polson (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 156)
    - Hershman gravesite, Polson (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 157)
    - Engdahl ranch gravesite (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 158)
    - Haze Lyon (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 159)
    - Herron ranch gravesite, Kalispell (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 160)
    - Chester museum grave rock (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 161)
    - Brackett creek gravesite (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 162)
    - John Daily (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 163)
    - J.S. Smith (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 164)
    - Hanks gravesite (negative only) (Box 71, Folder 12, Photographic-print 165)
  - Forts #166-176 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Fort Ellis (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 166-169)
    - Fort Logan (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 170)
    - Fort Benton (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 171-172)
    - Fort Benton (negative only) (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 173)
    - Fort Owen (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 174)
    - Fort Union (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 175)
    - Fort Collins, Colorado (Box 71, Folder 13, Photographic-print 176)
    - Doane-Hunter families (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 177-183)
    - Tennis tournament, Hunter's Hot Springs (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 177)
    - Gustavus C. Doane, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 178)
    - Doane tombstone (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 179)
    - Mary Hunter Doane, 1878 (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 180)
    - Mary Hunter Doane, circa 1880s (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 181)
    - Mrs. A.J. Hunter (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 182)
    - Reenactment of Doane's 1870 encampment at Yellowstone (Box 71, Folder 14, Photographic-print 183)
  - Montana State University/Montana State College #184-191 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Mount Baldy "M" (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 184)
    - Hedges Hall (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 185)
    - Old skating rink (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 186)
    - W.W. Freeman in Chemistry (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 187)
    - Morning devotions, Danforth Chapel (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 188)
    - Students leaving morning devotions (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 189)
    - Ken Ostermiller at Danforth Chapel (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 190)
    - Traphagen Hall (Box 71, Folder 15, Photographic-print 191)
  - Harriette Cushman #192-198 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Harriette Cushman, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 192)
    - Harriette Cushman, 1935 (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 193)
    - Harriette Cushman, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 194)
    - Harriette Cushman, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 195)
    - Harriette Cushman, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 196)
    - Harriette Cushman making a call as county agent, 1935 (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 197)
    - Harriette Cushman birth record (negative only) (Box 71, Folder 16, Photographic-print 198)
  - Christian Church #199-213 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - O.F. McHargue (Box 71, Folder 17, Photographic-print 199)
    - Church groups, J.E. Parker (Box 71, Folder 17, Photographic-print 200)
    - Church groups, A.L Chapman (Box 71, Folder 17, Photographic-print 201)
    - Christian Church Sunday school, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 17, Photographic-print 202)
    - Arthur J. Aikens (Box 71, Folder 17, Photographic-print 203)
    - Old parsonage moving, 1981 April 8 (Box 71, Folder 17, Photographic-print #205-213)
  - Christian Church #214-223 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - A.L Chapman (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 214)
    - E.T.C. Bennett (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 215)
    - John F. Ghormley (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 216)
    - Payne memorial church (artifact removed) (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 217)
    - A.L Chapman (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 218)
    - Reverend and Mrs. Arthur J. Aikens (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 219)
    - Grand Avenue Church, 1901 (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 220)
    - Grand Avenue Church, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 221)
    - Grand Avenue Church, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 222)
    - Grand Avenue Church, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 18, Photographic-print 223)
  - Christian Church #226-231 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - S. George Griffith (Box 71, Folder 19, Photographic-print 226)
    - James E. Parker (Box 71, Folder 19, Photographic-print 227)
    - Mark C. Cronenberger (Box 71, Folder 19, Photographic-print 228)
    - Grant H. Cole (Box 71, Folder 19, Photographic-print 229)
    - Everett Cecil (Box 71, Folder 19, Photographic-print 230)
    - Jeff C. Holder (Box 71, Folder 19, Photographic-print 231)
  - Indians and reservations #232-242 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - St. Mary's Mission, 1933 (Box 71, Folder 20, Photographic-print 232)
    - Botana and family (Box 71, Folder 20, Photographic-print 233)
    - Fort Peck Indian Reservation, street scene, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 20, Photographic-print 234)
    - Cree sundance lodge, 1906 (Box 71, Folder 20, Photographic-print 235-236)
    - Fort Peck cabin (Box 71, Folder 20, Photographic-print 237)
    - Browning midwinter fair, 1930s (Box 71, Folder 20, Photographic-print 238-242)
  - Indians-Antiquities and Archaeology #244-256 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Burial rocks, Sonnette site, near Broadus (Box 71, Folder 21, Photographic-print 244-253)
    - Projectile points from Keogh buffalo jump (Box 71, Folder 21, Photographic-print 254-255)
    - Madison buffalo jump, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 21, Photographic-print 256)
  - Indians-Antiquities #257-273 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Axe head (Box 71, Folder 22, Photographic-print 257)
    - Burlingame examining site, location unknown (Box 71, Folder 22, Photographic-print 258-259)
    - Burlingame examining site, Gallatin River near Spanish Creek, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 22, Photographic-print 260-269)
    - Rock etchings north of Broadview, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 22, Photographic-print 270-273)
  - Indians-Antiquities #274-304 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Carved ivory found near Glasgow, 1917 (Box 71, Folder 23, Photographic-print 274-276)
    - Blacktail cavern artifacts (Box 71, Folder 23, Photographic-print 277-298)
    - Medicine wheel near Sheridan, Wyoming (Box 71, Folder 23, Photographic-print 299-300)
    - Logan buffalo jump (negatives only) (Box 71, Folder 23, Photographic-print 301-303)
    - Sheep jump painting (negative only) (Box 71, Folder 23, Photographic-print 304)
  - Transportation #305-309 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Railroad track at Baker, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 24, Photographic-print 305)
    - Steamboat "OK" in 1908 (Box 71, Folder 24, Photographic-print 306)
    - Steamboats at Fort Benton (Box 71, Folder 24, Photographic-print 307)
    - First airplane at Eureka, 1915 (Box 71, Folder 24, Photographic-print 308-309)
  - Montana views and miscellany #310-327 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Hanging of Seachrist (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 310)
    - Vigilante charter, 1865 (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 311)
    - Old Faithful (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 312)
    - Gallatin River (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 313)
    - Bridger mountains (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 314)
    - Coyote (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 315)
    - Geyser (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 316)
    - Mountains (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 317)
    - Custer battlefield (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 318-319)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Archdeacon (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 320-323)
    - Arbor Lodge, Nebraska (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 324)
    - McGill museum exhibit (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 325)
    - Nob Castle Rock (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 326)
    - Black Butte (Box 71, Folder 25, Photographic-print 327)
  - Burlingame Africa trip slides, (not numbered), 1969 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Negatives (#1, 5, 7, 14, 15, 22, 23, 28, 30-33, 39, 45, 71-72, 90-92, 133, 134, 137-145, 159, 165, 173, 199, 203, 214-216, 220, 227, 228, 230-233, 258, 301-304, 308, 309) (Box 71, Folder 27)
- Maps, 12
  Printed and manuscript maps collected or created by Burlingame in association with his research interests. The maps have been organized according to the issuing agency and are either exclusively Montana or the American West. Some of the manuscript maps were created for Burlingame's book The Montana Frontier. Box 72 also contains oversize materials removed from previous series.
  - Manuscript maps (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Montana Highway Department County Maps, 1941-1963 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Forest Service Bureau of Land Management (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Western United States (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Bozeman family tree (from series 1) (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Montana State University instructors (from series 7) (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Certificates and awards (from series 10) (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Microfilm, 13
  Microfilmed primary source materials collected by Burlingame from various institutions in the United States and Canada pertaining to a wide variety of historical subjects and persons. Institutions from which the microfilm was ordered includes Harvard, Yale, New York Public Library, Missouri Historical Society, and the Manitoba Archives. Permission to use any of this material must be granted by the institutions holding the original documents. Information in brackets has been taken from the order form Burlingame filled out for some institutions and may refer to that institution's control number of the documents that were duplicated. Film in boxes 101-134 appear to be "home made" by Burlingame himself from original documents whose origin cannot be determined.
  - Manitoba Archives: Johnstone, William - Notes of a trip to the Rocky Mountains in 1866 (Box 73)
  - Yale University Library: Upham, H.D. - Letters, 1865 (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Freeman, H.B. - Journal [Whithington 204], 1867 (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Greene, Francis Vinton - Voyage of FVG from Sweet Grass Hills to Bismarck [Withington 230] (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Thomas, W. Kent - Little Big Horn [article] (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Greene, Francis Vinton - Letter from Virginia City, 1875 August 25 (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Hempstead, Thomas - Letterbook [Withington 231], 1821 (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Baird, George William - Indian campaigning with General Miles [WA MSS S911 B163] (Box 74)
  - Yale University Library: Hedges, Cornelius - Diaries, 1849-1851; 1856; 1863; 1867-1882 (Box 75)
  - Yale University Library: Hedges, Cornelius - Diaries, 1851-1855 (Box 76)
  - Yale University Library: Hedges, Cornelius - Diaries, 1883-1907 (Box 77)
  - Montana Historical Society: Hedges, Cornelius - Diary, 1865 (Box 78)
  - University of North Carolina: Richmond, Theodore - Papers [Collection 632] (Box 79)
  - University of North Carolina: Gibson/Humphries papers [Collection 922] (Box 79)
  - Yale University Library: Bond, Samuel - Journal of the Fisk expedition [Withington 39], 1862 (Box 80)
  - Yale University Library: English, William - Field diary of WE, 1876 (Box 80)
  - Yale University Library: Wilson, James S.R. - Journal of a trip to Yellowstone Park, 1875 (Box 80)
  - Yale University Library: Nauser, Samuel - Letters to his sister, 1862 (Box 80)
  - New York Public Library: Bond, Fred - Diary, 1876 (Box 81)
  - New York Public Library: Sydendham diary (Lt. 2nd Infantry), 1889-1890 (Box 81)
  - New York Public Library: Astor papers, letter, 1814 (Box 81)
  - New York Public Library: Montana-Upper Missouri Valley Research Material (Box 81)
  - New York Public Library: Coon, Homer - Recollections, Nez Perce Indians (Box 81)
  - New York Public Library: Brown, Edwin M. - Account of expedition, 1867-1877 (Box 81)
  - New York Public Library: Greene, Francis Vinton - U.S. Northern Boundary Commission Letters, 1872-1876 (Box 82)
  - New York Public Library: Howard, Wade - A journey from Tipton, Missouri to Virginia City, 1865 (Box 83)
  - Harvard University Library: Albright, Edward L. - St. Peters Mission (Box 84)
  - Harvard University Library: Blake, Frank - The "locus" of the soul in the body (Box 84)
  - Harvard University Library: Brown, Earl W. - A problem in approximate trisection (Box 84)
  - Harvard University Library: Clinch, Thomas Anthony - Historical Backgrounds of Custer's Last Stand [All of the above are theses from Carroll College], 1949 (Box 84)
  - Harvard University Library: Healy, John J. - Interview by Forest Crissey, 1899 May 29 (Box 84)
  - New York Public Library: Greene, Francis Vinton - Diary of a trip to Yellowstone Park, 1875 (Box 85)
  - New York Public Library: Berthold, E.L. - Explorations in Idaho and Montana in 1878 (Box 86)
  - New York Public Library: Brown, J. - Traditions of the Blackfeet (Box 86)
  - Missouri Historical Society, St. Louis, Excerpts From: Choteau-Pampin collection, 1829-1850 (Box 87)
  - Missouri Historical Society, St. Louis, Excerpts From: Drips papers, 1842 (Box 87)
  - Missouri Historical Society, St. Louis, Excerpts From: William Clark papers (Box 87)
  - Missouri Historical Society, St. Louis, Excerpts From: Sibley papers, 1819-1864 (Box 87)
  - New York Historical Society: In Memorium: Edwin R. Purple, 1881 (Box 88)
  - New York Historical Society: Excerpts from Edwin R. Purple papers (Box 89)
  - Manitoba Archives, Selections From: Alexander Morris papers (Box 90)
  - Manitoba Archives, Selections From: Adams G. Archibald Papers (Box 90)
  - Manitoba Archives, Selections From: Louis Riel papers (Box 90)
  - Manitoba Archives: negative reel (Box 91)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Larouque, F.A. "Journal of the Missouri River, 1804-1805" [MG 19 C1 Volume 3] (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: McKenzie, Charles, "Account of Missouri Indians, 1804" [MG 19 C2 vol9] (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Department of Interior-Dominion Lands Branch (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Journey to Mountain House, Winter, 1870-1871 (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: British Minister 1330 "Alleged outrage by U.S. Troops upon settlers at White River" (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Fletcher, H.C. 2679 "Apprehended attacks by Indians on boundary, letter from Captain Cameron" (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Colonial Secretary 4561 "Letter from Earl of Carnarvon and from Sir E. Thorton on discovery of gold in Black Hills" (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Indian Affairs 121007 "Conditions of Canadian Indians in U.S. and Sioux, letter from Fort Belknap, 1879" (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: Devins, J.S. 157337 "Report on Mormon settlement at Cardston" (Box 92)
  - Public Archives of Canada, Ottowa: RG 18, Series B, volume 5 "Rondeau and Alexis History of Southern Saskatchewan" (Box 92)
  - Library of Congress: Evans, Charles, Diary, 1853 July - September (Box 93)
  - Library of Congress: Brown, Edward B. "Terror in the Badlands: Journal of the Miles Expedition, 1876-1877" (Box 93)
  - Harvard University Library: Selections from the Oswald G. Villard papers regarding Burton K. Wheeler, Frederick Billings, and Henry Villard (Box 94)
  - Missouri Historical Society, St. Louis: Fort Union Letter Book [Choteau Collection], 1833-1835 (Box 95)
  - University of Missouri-Western Historical Manuscripts Collection: Wibaux, Pierre - Papers, 1881-1929 (Box 96)
  - Library of Congress: Thomas J. Walsh papers - Correspondence pertaining to women's suffrage (Box 97)
  - Montana Historical Society: Leases on mortgaged lands, circa 1850s (Box 98)
  - Montana Historical Society: David, Christopher C - Diary, 1879-1881 (Box 99)
  - National Archives: Records of the Washington Superintendency of Indian Affairs, 1853-1874 (Box 100)
  - National Archives: Letters from employees assigned to the eastern district, Flathead agency and Blackfeet agency, 1853-1863 (Box 100)
  - Burlingame Reels: Indian Affairs - charges against (Box 101)
  - Burlingame Reels: Flathead Agency Observations 29p (Box 102)
  - Burlingame Reels: Miscellaneous Indian Agency 38p (Box 103)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - letters received + 45p, 1880 August 15 (Box 104)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - Letters Received + 33p, 1881 July (Box 105)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - Letters Received (Roll 2) + 34p, 1881 July (Box 106)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - Letters sent + 19p, 1882 May (Box 107)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - Letters sent + 34p, 1883 May (Box 108)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - Letters sent 27p, 1883 September (Box 109)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - Letters sent 36p, 1889 June (Box 110)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Maginnis - letters sent August + 37p, 1884 August (Box 111)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Belknap 20p, 1873-1876 (Box 112)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Custer, research paper by Richard Bowler, 1965 (Box 113)
  - Burlingame Reels: Letters sent from Fort Custer 21p, 1877 (Box 114)
  - Burlingame Reels: Letters sent from Fort Custer 28p, 1879 (Box 115)
  - Burlingame Reels: Letters sent from Fort Custer 28p, 1883 (Box 116)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Belknap 1873-1876 43p (Box 117)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Peck - 31p+ 12-44 (Box 118)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Peck - 37p (Box 119)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Peck - 1874 24p (Box 120)
  - Burlingame Reels: Fort Benton - Letters sent 1869 + 48p (Box 121)
  - Burlingame Reels: Stevens Treaty Roll #1, 1855 (Box 122)
  - Burlingame Reels: Stevens Roll #2, 1855 (Box 123)
  - Burlingame Reels: Stevens Treaty Roll #3, 1855 (Box 124)
  - Burlingame Reels: Stevens Treaty Roll #4 - 31p Roll #5 - 12p = 43p, 1855 (Box 125)
  - Burlingame Reels: Doane's Report on Pease Exp. Roll #1 33p (Box 126)
  - Burlingame Reels: Doane's Report on Pease Exp. Roll #2-1/2 Dark- (Box 127)
  - Burlingame Reels: Doane's Report on Pease Exp. Roll #3 31p (Box 128)
  - Burlingame Reels: Doane Materials regarding Yellowstone Park Superintendent (Box 129)
  - Burlingame Reels: Doane - Miscellaneous In Fort Ellis Materials 26p (Box 130)
  - Burlingame Reels: Doane - Miscellaneous In Fort Ellis Materials 31p (Box 131)
  - Burlingame Reels: J.V. Bogart - Yellowstone Expedition 10p (Box 132)
  - Burlingame Reels: 1870 Report of Inspector General Hardie Rec. The Baker Exp. 11p Col. Bakers Report 3p. 11p Col (Box 133)
  - Burlingame Reels: Inspector General Hardies Report and Record of Baker 1870 Expedition. 39p (Box 134)
- Audiotapes, 14
  Recordings made or collected by Merrill Burlingame on a wide variety of research topics. Among the interviewees are Malcolm Story and Harriette Cushman, along with Burlingame himself. Tapes 1 through 20 are on audiocassette. Tapes 21-30 are audiotape reels.
  - The Death of John Bozeman - M.G. Burlingame - Robin Machab Side A=#1 Side B=#2, 1983 March 31 (Box 135, Audiocassette 1)
  - Death of John Bozeman…Side A=#3 (90 minutes) (Box 135, Audiocassette 2)
  - Malcolm Story, Sons of Am. Revolution 2-22-1983 Side A=#1, Side B=#2 (60 minutes), 1983 February 22 (Box 135, Audiocassette 3)
  - Malcolm Story 1st 1/3 (Side A) (90 minutes) Spring Hill August 1982 - October 7, 1982 (Side B) (Box 135, Audiocassette 4)
  - Malcolm Story (90 minutes) (Box 135, Audiocassette 5)
  - Lewis and Clark Pageant at Headwaters State Park, 1982 August (Box 135, Audiocassette 6)
  - Remembering A.H. Strand -3-15-1982 #1, #2 (90 minutes) Faculty group at Margaret Paisley home, 1982 March 15 (Box 135, Audiocassette 7)
  - Mr. Skillman #1, #2 (60 minutes) (Box 135, Audiocassette 8)
  - Mr. Skillman #3, #4 (60 minutes) (Box 135, Audiocassette 9)
  - Mr. Skillman #5 (60 minutes) (Box 135, Audiocassette 10)
  - Mary Sloan Interview (Box 135, Audiocassette 11)
  - Mary Sloan Interview (Box 135, Audiocassette 12)
  - Ray Mentzer - Fort Ellis Gallatin County Historical Society, January 29, 1981 (Side 1); Bayard Todd - Gallatin Gateway, March 12, 1981 (Side 2), 1981 January 29, 1981 March 12 (Box 135, Audiocassette 13)
  - "A Rose…" re: 4H delegates going to Boise, Idaho (Box 135, Audiocassette 14)
  - "A Rose…" (Box 135, Audiocassette 15)
  - Harriet Cushman interview by Kit Miller (Box 135, Audiocassette 16)
  - John Colter (Box 135, Audiocassette 17)
  - Christmas story (Box 135, Audiocassette 18)
  - Harriette Cushman (Box 135, Audiocassette 19)
  - Merrill Burlingame, interview by Susan Gibb, 1992 October 17 (Box 135, Audiocassette 20)
  - Unidentified family interview* (Box 135, Audiocassette 21)
  - Gallatin Gateway 10-3-65*, 1965 October 3 (Box 135, Audiocassette 22)
  - Gallatin Gateway 10-3-65*, 1965 October 3 (Box 135, Audiocassette 23)
  - Mr. Robers, Mrs. Copping* (Box 135, Audiocassette 24)
  - Mrs. Frasur and Mother*, 1966 November 19 (Box 135, Audiocassette 25)
  - Wiley Davis - the Chinese in Virginia City* (Box 135, Audiocassette 26)
  - Mrs. Brainard 11-66*, 1967 January 20 (Box 135, Audiocassette 27)
  - Mrs. Brainard 12-66* (Box 135, Audiocassette 28)
  - Martha Palffy (W.P.C)* (Box 135, Audiocassette 29)
  - Gene Quaw at Bozeman City Hall w/ Mia History Group(W.P.C)* (Box 135, Audiocassette 30)
  - Fred C. Krieg (two reels), 1966 February 26 (Box 135, Audiocassette 31)
  - Warren McGee Bozeman Trail lecture* (tape stored separately), 1968 (Box 135, Audiocassette 32)